Chocolates save us from many things, especially emotional distress.
巧克力能让我们免受许多事情的困扰，尤其是情绪上的痛苦。
They comfort us in times of trouble, calming down a racing heart by channelling happy calories inside us.
身处困境时，它们给我们安慰：把带来快乐的热量输送到我们体内，从而让狂跳的心平静下来。
We all have faith in chocolates to delight us in an instant!
我们都相信，巧克力能在转眼间让我们开心起来！
Recently, chocolate lovers were heartbroken as scientists claimed that chocolates could become extinct by 2050!
最近，有科学家声称到2050年巧克力可能会灭绝，这让巧克力爱好者们心碎不已！
But hey, we have some happy news for you.
不过，嘿，我们有一些好消息要告诉你。
Scientists can still help save chocolates from dying out!
科学家仍然能够帮助巧克力免于灭绝！
If you are not aware as to why scientists made the statement about the death of this wonderful thing, let us tell you the facts.
如果你不清楚科学家为何会就这一美妙之物的消亡发表这番言论，那就让我们把事实告诉你吧。
Chocolate trees, whose seeds are used to make chocolate, grow in the tropical plant world and require very specific weather conditions to prosper.
可可树的种子用来制作巧克力；这种树生长在热带植物世界里，需要非常特定的天气条件才能茁壮成长。
Now, fifty percent of the world’s cocoa beans come from two countries in West Africa: Côte d’Ivoire and Ghana.
目前，全世界百分之五十的可可豆来自西非的两个国家：科特迪瓦和加纳。
Scientists believe that both of these countries will experience a 3.8 °F temperature increase by 2050 due to global warming, endangering the cacao farms in the rainforests.
科学家认为，由于全球变暖，到2050年这两个国家的气温都将上升3.8华氏度，危及雨林中的可可种植园。
These farms will then have to be shifted to cooler mountainous areas, which are the natural habitat of wildlife.
届时，这些种植园将不得不迁往更凉爽的山区，而那里是野生动物的天然栖息地。
This will lead to some tough decisions: whether to grow chocolate or save wildlife.
这将带来一些艰难的抉择：是种植巧克力，还是保护野生动物。
Unfortunately, the crisis of global warming has already had a serious negative impact on cacao farms’ yields, leading to the prices of chocolates skyrocketing.
不幸的是，全球变暖危机已经对可可种植园的产量造成了严重的负面影响，导致巧克力价格飞涨。
Scientists, however, are trying to find a long-term and eco-friendly solution to this problem!
然而，科学家们正设法为这一问题找到一个长期而又环保的解决方案！
They are trying to modify the species with a gene-editing technology, which will transform the seedlings into a species that survives even in a drier and warmer climate.
他们正尝试用一种基因编辑技术改造这一物种，这项技术将把幼苗转变为一种即使在更干燥、更温暖的气候中也能存活的物种。
According to a report by Business Insider, in the University of California’s new bio-sciences building, tiny green cacao seedlings are lined up in refrigerated greenhouses for a new experiment using a technology called CRISPR.
据《商业内幕》报道，在加利福尼亚大学新建的生物科学大楼里，小小的绿色可可树幼苗一排排地摆放在冷藏温室中，准备用于一项采用CRISPR技术的新实验。
This technology, which manipulates the DNA of plants, is already being used across the world to make plants tougher and cheaper.
这项操控植物DNA的技术已在世界各地得到应用，用来让植物变得更强健、更便宜。
Similarly, in this unconventional experiment, scientists will make tiny, precise changes to the DNA of the seedlings to make the cocoa crops survive in warmer and drier climates.
同样，在这项非常规的实验中，科学家们将对幼苗的DNA作出微小而精确的改动，让可可作物能在更温暖、更干燥的气候中存活。